Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
No living creature was harmed
during the filming of this series.
Episode 102
I will cut off your head, Osman.
You can't even cut my beard.
Come with me
You tried to kill me, right?
There is no going back for this anymore.
You will die, Öktem.
If I were to do my job with the arrow...
I will not draw the sword, you infidel!
Beys!
If your intention is to seek justice...
I say you have to wait for Osman Bey.
Don't test my patience, Öktem Bey.
Why don't you listen?
Stop.
If someone overstepped his bounds...
he is.
My blood has been shed
on this land, Turgut Bey.
I won't ignore it.
- Soldiers!
- Alps!
I say we will resolve this
matter calmly, Öktem Bey.
But you don't listen to me!
You pull the sword.
You shoot arrows.
I won't compromise with you anymore.
You will be arrested.
Turgut Bey.
Please, do something.
Where is Osman Bey?
Do what you want to do, Turgut Bey?
The talk is over.
Don't do it, Öktem Bey.
Don't.
You are bleeding, Osman.
I will make all your blood flow.
Come and see.
You can't defeat me Osman.
Let's see.
Another one to get revenge for.
When you have no more blood to bleed...
there will be no revenge you take.
Emperor Andronikos...
invites you to meet him.
If someone doesn't want to stop...
I'll have to go with his body.
Why are you standing, Beys?
Draw your swords.
When you get into trouble, you come
to the tribe of Öktem Bey.
Why this hesitation now?
Don't, beys.
Who draws his sword now...
he pulls his sword on Osman Bey.
Your eyes are blind to see the truth.
I won't let you drag the Beys
into that darkness.
How dare you, Alçiçek Hatun?
Öktem Bey.
If you don't trust justice and draw
the sword before it's time...
you become a rebel.
And you know that killing the rebel is
our duty. Don't do this.
Be careful, Alps.
Turgut Bey.
Alps have surrounded the tribe.
They're waiting for your command.
There is no going back for this.
Trust in the justice of Osman Bey.
Tell your Alps...
to put down their swords, Öktem Bey.
What justice are you
talking about, Turgut Bey?
Does Osman have justice?
This ignoble that you brought
into our tribe....
his hands are stained with
the blood of our heroes.
Both were stained with my brother's blood.
Osman Bey's balance is off.
We will not leave my father
a victim of his justice.
We don't trust
to the words of the infidels.
We stand behind Öktem Bey.
We stand behind you with the Alps.
What you are saying is not
acceptable, Uraz Bey.
Do you want to make
the brothers kill each other?
They are all of us, and they are
all of our blood.
Öktem Bey.
Give up before it gets any worse.
Come on.
You...
Who are you protecting, Commander?
I only protect Rome, Commander Olof.
Ophelia wanted to kill the emperor.
Osman was the reason for her escape.
Commander Remus!
If you protect him...
I will kill you and kill him.
Osman Bey...
Welcome back to save Rome.
I give you my respect.
The emperor is waiting for you.
Thank you.
Then...
Let's go see the emperor.
The Emperor
Is he in a state to
give orders?
What are you up to?
Sarkis ran away.
Ophelia ran away.
It is not you who will do justice.
Know your limits.
You speak too confidently as
someone who protects traitors.
You are too brave for someone whose axe
is useless.
If you don't break your
courage, your head will break.
Let's not make the emperor
wait any longer.
Let's go.
And you too, Commander.
The emperor called you too.
With your permission, Turgut Bey.
Öktem Bey.
They will kill all these warriors
with your word.
Turgut Bey is right.
The blood spilled
will be our blood.
Give up.
We are behind you.
Alps!
Put down your swords.
You have heard your Bey.
Put the swords in their sheaths, come on.
Soldiers.
Don't do it, Bey.
Whoever puts gold in your tribe will put
the rope around your neck tomorrow.
Put your sword down, Hatun.
Father.
From now on...
It's up to you, Turgut Bey.
For the safety of my tribe...
I will surrender to the
justice of Osman Bey.
Trust our scale of justice.
You did the right thing.
The emperor will ask me
to cut off your head.
You caused Ophelia to escape.
I will be your executioner.
I will know who you serve.
Then you will see who
will be the executioner...
who will be the victim.
Odin's soldiers serve only Odin.
And the emperor, of course.
You tricked Ophelia's mind.
She tried to kill her father.
The emperor knows everything.
This will be your death decision.
Look at me.
Do you see a frightened man?
Allah wrote my fate.
I will not be afraid of the
words of an idolater like you.
Even if Odin himself is the one
holding your ropes...
I will find it.
Olof.
The emperor is waiting for you.
May Jesus sanctify you, Sarkis.
I was very afraid.
What if something
happened to you?
Was that help you talked about from Osman?
Yes, and he did not disappoint us.
And what about my father?
Is there any news about him?
Is he alive?
If something had happened
to the emperor...
those who wanted the throne
would have already moved.
Someone is coming.
Don't think about it, princess.
Your predictions may be correct
I promise you, princess.
I will learn your father's condition.
You will be fine, princess.
You and your dad too.
I believe you Sarkis.
Stop, don't run, stop.
Catch them!
I had told you, emperor.
Be careful.
Your position doesn't want negligence.
How careful I can be when it
was my daughter who attacked me?
Look at this.
My daughter is poisoning me.
And the enemy will save me.
Osman who saved your life today...
saved Ophelia, who wanted to kill you.
You can't forgive him for this.
Ophelia's death will be at my hands.
But she will speak first.
She will tell us about Frigg, the
snake on my land.
He caused her to run away.
He killed my men.
From this city...
While no one in the palace knows
that I have been poisoned...
How do know, Osman Bey?
And you, Olof?
Did you know?
I...
I crucify anyone who even thinks of this.
How did you know, Osman Bey?
You're fine because I know.
Don't check with me about this.
The eye that watches the palace, only
covets the throne, Emperor.
I will pluck out that eye and
present it as a gift to Odin.
Damn! Who did this?
It is enough.
First it poisons me, then it
makes me better.
Is that what you're saying, Olof?
And what about Frigg?
Ophelia?
Did you know about them
thanks to your spies?
No.
Kantakuzenos told me.
Ophelia has sent a spy called Frigg to
my land to wreak havoc.
First, she will talk about this.
But Olof wants to kill her.
It was my daughter who attacked
you and me, Osman Bey.
But the throne is not managed by mercy.
She will be killed as soon as she is seen.
No one will die before I hear what I want.
The sedition on your land has
reached my land.
Frigg is on your land now.
And Ophelia will go there.
I will kill her.
You won't get between me
and my daughter, Osman Bey.
My land, my matter.
I'll give you your daughter after
I take what I want...
my friend Andronikos.
Be my guest tonight, Osman Bey.
We haven't finished talking yet.
Thank you, Emperor!
Excuse me now.
What is this, brother?
Greek gold!
What happened?
Please friends, don't stop until
you reach Yenişehir.
What's happening? What's going ON?
Come on, Cerkutay, come on.
Come on, Cerkutay.
Kantakuzenos.
Your wound is deep, Kantakuzenos.
Come with us to host you in Yenişehir.
If I didn't destroy the tribe over the
heads of these rude ones...
It was because of my trust in you.
If the balance of your
justice is spoiled...
know that I will not hesitate
to apply my justice.
Calm, Kantakuzenos.
Hatun.
Don't worry, Hatun.
Öktem Bey.
Let's go, Turgut Bey.
Our soldiers will stay in the tribe until
the last moment after we're gone.
Don't make mistakes and don't rebel.
Nothing like this will happen.
What you say will happen, Bey.
However, Turgut Bey...
if Osman Bey does any injustice...
and if you are blinded to the truth...
then you won't be able to stop
us even if you all come.
The balance of justice isn't
spoiled, don't worry, Bengi Hatun.
Let's go.
Come on, Kantakuzenos.
I will hold you accountable for what
we are experiencing now.
I won't ignore it.
Don't forget this day.
There is nothing that we
can not account for.
Our place and our homeland are
clear, come when you want.
Come on.
The days will surely come when we will
hold them accountable.
However, we will not forget those...
who pretended to be by our side and
didn't defend us with their swords.
Bengi hatun.
Do you think we didn't stand behind Öktem
Bey because we let them take him?
If they try to sacrifice Öktem Bey
because of the infidel's game...
we will go to Yenişehir and take it from
them by force.
Osman Bey.
Whenever we meet, we stand
up to each other.
We will know who is the traitor
and who is the friend.
And when I know this,
I will do what I have to do.
I can control my axe.
But if my anger controls me...
It is my axe that rules me.
When I got to the ring, I
went in to kill everyone.
I didn't know we were in the same place.
But when sinners fall into my hands...
my axe will cut many heads.
However, today...
please accept my apologies, Osman Bey.
An apology is the hallmark of the brave.
But forgiveness is an attribute
of the strong.
The smell of innocent blood is still on
your hand that you hold for peace.
A warrior's hand must be
stained with blood.
There was no innocent person
among those ı killed.
I hope we never meet again as enemies.
I say this for your safety.
When the time comes, we will see
who is innocent and who is guilty.
- Was he sincerely asking for forgiveness?
- No.
He's trying to make me lower my shield.
But that's part of the game.
I will definitely kill him.
We carry healing and
death within us as well.
- Are you going to do this in the palace, my Bey?
- I won't go.
He's coming to kill me.
But not in the palace, but
in the place I want.
I will find out who he serves to...
and then I will hang his body at
the gate of Constantinople.
Osman will not stop.
You will follow his footsteps
like a shadow.
What's on your mind, Olof?
The gods want an offering. (sacrifice)
But I want revenge.
Both will happen.
Osman will die when he leaves the palace.
Would killing Osman make
the emperor our enemy?
I make whoever I want our enemy.
But it is not me who will kill
Osman, but Ophelia.
Ophelia the Demon.
She's such a demon that she
poisoned her father first...
then she killed Osman.
There are people who are worse
than us, Frodi.
There are people
who are worse than us.
Yenişehir
Kantakuzenos has a deep
wound, Malhun Hatun.
His condition got worse while
we came here.
It would be good to get the
doctors to treat him.
Alps, prepare the guest hall immediately
and tell the doctors (healers) to come.
Come on, give it up right away.
My wound is a minor wound, and
there is no need to worry.
The doctors will decide that.
Come on, then.
Marta.
Malhun Hatun.
How is your hand?
It's better now, thank you.
We have brought the last
pieces of cloth needed.
How are you?
Is the city safe, Malhun Hatun?
Actually I'm not used to this, and
I feel a little scared.
We have so many enemies, Marta.
However, our courage will
overcome them all.
Don't be so afraid.
Why are you so afraid?
Constantinople
Come here.
My brothers.
Tell me! Is exile difficult?
There is nothing difficult
about this, my Bey.
We know how important our job is
and we're watching Emperor.
We will always watch this fool so that
our path to conquests is always paved.
The valiants are on
guard in East and West.
Whoever has solid intelligence
holds the reins of power in his hand.
This place is the source
of the strife that exists on our lands.
But exile is the way to home.
So tell me, what is Ophelia's condition?
She's scared.
She is accused of
trying to kill her father.
But I don't know if she did that or not.
There is no importance to that.
Olof and the Emperor want her dead.
It is important that we have her.
We will take her with us on
our return to Yenişehir...
so that we know if she is
innocent or guilty.
The princess has been with
me for a long time, my Bey.
And if you ask me what I see, she is
a victim, not an oppressor.
No, this is not the time when we will
depend on what we see or hear.
If we're going to depend on what we see...
I should behead
Öktem Bey.
Open the door, brother.
We were together.
We fought the infidels together.
Now, you're throwing me in your cell.
Thank you.
If a Turkmen is hurt...
we are the ones who will fall, Öktem Bey.
Our pain is one, our grief is one.
However, we have to secure the justice.
You can't keep people inside
your dungeons, Boran.
But now you give me a lot of advice.
There is no justice that
can be trusted, Boran.
Öktem Bey, we show you respect even
though all the evidence is against you.
However, you have to know your
limit and your position well.
You believe the accusations.
I will bear all these slanders but...
you got your hands dirty with
these false slanders anyway.
Sufficient for us is Allah.
Öktem Bey.
So, we wash our hands with the blood of
the one who stained us with these slanders.
First prove your innocence.
Inshallah.
Come on, brother.
Brother.
I don't hear anything and
I don't understand.
But what I see hurts my heart.
What's going on, brother?
They say that there is
good in all evil, Cerkutay.
I wish I could be in your place now, brother.
You don't hear a word.
It is true what you say, my brother.
A warrior can't stay without
food or horse.
Oh.
Cerkutay.
Don't you really hear, brother?
Or are you playing a game on me?
No, no.
You don't really hear.
Come on brother, come on.
tell me.
How did this wound happen?
It's a serious wound.
But it doesn't hurt.
It makes me weak.
It's very difficult.
What is difficult, my Bey?
I went through all these wars
and was not affected.
You know.
Shall I say?
It's a heart wound.
Wait, I'll boil you soup.
It'll do you good.
But you will suffer a lot.
What are you looking at, my Bey?
Love is a test.
Either you love her...
and she doesn't love you...
Or you two love each other...
And this time, various misfortunes
come and befall you.
Love crushes us.
It is true what you say.
But I insist, Ülgen Hatun.
On this bumpy road...
I'll walk until my feet bleed.
Inshallah, walk. Let the paths be yours.
But, tell me first. You were in the tribe
all that time.
Did you talk to the girl? Is
she interested?
I do not know.
She didn't even say my name.
Don't say that.
Fire fell in the heart of the Alçiçek.
Subasi.
Welcome, Bala Hatun.
Things got complicated in
Yenişehir in your absence.
The system is new.
But you must take precautions first.
Are things to get complicated in
Yenişehir because you are not there?
I scolded all the Alps.
The number of Alps in dungeon increased.
Nothing like this will
happen again, Inshallah.
Good.
But something comes to my mind.
You increased the number of
Alps in dungeon earlier.
What is the reason for this?
Was there an intrusion attempt
that we don't know about?
Is there anything you would
like to say, Subasi?
The girl entered Osman Bey's dungeon...
and wounded Subasi...
then she got out and went as
if nothing had happened, right?
Which girl hurt you?
Alçiçek?
You represent justice...
and form the system, Subasi.
If you did it, what would
the warriors do?
Well, you did this.
You made this mistake.
How do you hide this?
Alçiçek was very angry because
of what happened to her uncle.
However, before...
She tried to kill you, Aktemur.
Is there more than this?
She didn't try to kill me, Bala Hatun.
It's a small wound.
It went wrong when I tried to block it.
In that mission, you are not Aktemur.
You are the Subasi.
Whoever tried to kill you
tried to corrupt Yenişehir.
You're blind.
The girl tried to kill you.
Is that girl more important
than your life and your job?
Mother.
I don't put anyone before my job.
Yeah, I saw it.
Is that why you protect the girl
who tried to kill you?
It's the lane map.
Tell me, what's Olof doing?
We watched him.
He sets up a trap with his soldiers.
There are few soldiers here.
It is suitable for trap.
He will attack here.
He will come for you, my Bey.
We'll take Olof tonight...
and we know for whom he works.
The source of his courage is
knowing that I'm alone here.
He won't stop until he gets what he wants.
Even exile is a home for us.
Turks will never be alone.
Don't hide.
You can show up.
Merchant Vassilis.
Hasan Alp, my Bey.
Waiting for your order.
Maid Hera.
Sister Gökçe is at your
command, Osman Bey.
They are the fruits of the seeds
that we planted years ago.
These formations are older than our age.
It will add strength to our
strength for generations, Inshallah.
I have three sons.
I raised them all to serve the country.
Mashallah!
Even if we are in the peace period...
do not take your eyes off the enemy.
Thank you.
It's time to pluck out the enemy's eye.
Start the preparations.
Öktem tribe
The great Beys of my tribe...
We came to this frontier to conquer.
However, they want to sacrifice our Bey
for the treacherous games of the enemy.
You know your Bey very well.
For the safety of his tribe, he remained
silent despite this slander...
and surrendered himself.
He is silent.
But I'm not silent.
I will not throw my Bey into the
fire that the infidels set.
Many of our Alps...
our valiants...
and now this slander!
The infidels entered among us...
and they stained our
land with their dirty gold!
Osman.
If Osman works...
with the infidels to get a
place with the Emperor...
and tries to punish Öktem Bey, his
comrade in war...
then no one will be able to stop me.
I will collapse that land!
With or without you!
My Beys, going down
this road takes courage.
The end of this path is not obeying Osman's orders...
and rebellion.
Even if there is only one
person behind me...
I'm going this way.
And now I ask you...
When the time comes and I draw my sword...
Will you be by my side?
Or will you stand against me?
We are with you, Bengi Hatun.
We keep our words.
We will not leave
Öktem Bey alone.
Let Osman Bey think about the rest.
Mother.
I wish we waited for court first.
Osman Bey trusts my father.
- Now...
- Alçiçek!
What are you saying?
Why do you sit aside
and remain silent?
They killed your uncle.
They are about to kill your father.
Will you send your father to death?
We won't send, mother.
Since Osman Bey won't come...
It makes no sense for me
to stay here any longer.
I will go.
just chill.
We won't let you go anywhere
while you're like this, you know.
But I also know you
don't stick to your words.
Osman Bey is sending me to the
Öktem tribe and he is not there.
Where is he?
If Osman Bey wanted this, you
would have known where he is.
What you know is enough.
If you have another
request, let us know.
Until then...
You are our guest.
In that case, I want you to bring
me the best cloth seller in your city.
At least I will get rid of these clothes.
Okay.
So, Bengi Hatun gathers Beys.
The split is coming soon.
Now, Osman has a big wound.
He has, my Bey.
Shall I make this
wound bleed?
We did what you said, my Bey.
You did.
You did your job well.
Now, it's my turn.
I buried the man in the
middle of the tent, my Bey.
Good.
In due time, get him out of the place
where you buried him...
and get rid of it.
Your order, my Bey.
But since we can kill him...
Why do we hurt him, my Bey?
To rub that wound.
Put this in your mind.
I don't care to gather strength.
I want to collect gold.
Let them fight.
So that they will ruin their reputation.
Merchants will come and find me.
I will get a lot of gold out of that wound.
Understood, right, Huseyin?
I understand, I understand, my Bey.
Good.
Now I'll take the gold that
came out of the Öktem tribe.
Find me reliable men quickly.
I will not let the infidels get that gold.
Hüseyin.
Your order, my Bey.
If you come before you find that gold...
don't let me see you.
Your order, my Bey.
Constantinople
Emperor's Palace
Constantinople.
My Bey.
I understand everything but...
What is your primary goal?
My goal...
is to set foot in the land of the infidels.
My goal is to make the banner
of Islam fly all over the world.
That's why you protect the emperor.
No.
I don't just protect the emperor.
I use him.
I even interfere in state affairs.
I keep the enemy by my side.
I keep them by my side...
to have a chance to spoil this
game when the time comes.
We will be fine.
Our goal is the emperor, Osman
The emperor.
The emperor sits on the throne
as long as we want.
Our goal is Byzantium.
Our goal will be great.
So that we will be great too.
We will crush the Byzantines.
And we will become a state, Inshallah.
I heard you were up to
something, Bengi Hatun.
What is happening here? Why
did you gather the Beys?
Why did you come, Malhun Hatun?
Turgut Bey harmed my tribe.
Do you want to harm the rest?
No, Bengi Hatun.
I came to share your pain.
But I didn't like what I
saw or what I heard.
You say we hurt...
and we put salt on the wound.
I don't want your mercy.
It is clear that you are
chasing big goals.
But I will not allow this.
Why did you gather the Beys, Bengi Hatun?
What is your goal? Tell the truth.
Malhun Hatun.
This is my tribe, this is my tent.
I gather my Beys and Alps whenever I want.
I don't need to consult
anyone about anything.
You will, Hatun!
You'll consult Osman with every move you
make for the sake of your tribe and people.
What have we learned from
his advice to date?
My brother is under the ground
because we listened to your words.
My husband is in the dungeon
because we trusted you.
From now on, I won't consult you.
What are you implying, Hatun?
What is our fault?
It turns out that gold is in your tribe.
Are we the ones who
put that gold in your tribe?
You accuse Osman Bey for everything
happens in your tribe.
But this anger is not good.
This anger will make you wrong.
It's not me who make mistakes.
It is you who make mistakes.
You have brought that
infidel into your palace.
That dog's hands are stained
with the blood of a brave men.
Instead of killing him...
you bandaged his wounds.
Not everyone is our
friend, Bengi Hatun.
If we helped Kantakuzenos, we
have our reasons.
I'm not good at politics, and I
don't like complicated business like that.
But there is one thing I know.
From now on, we are not on the same side.
Okay then, Bengi Hatun.
So, we deal with you as you said.
My eyes will be on you until the court.
Be careful.
If you make one mistake, you will be
next to your husband in the dungeon.
We'll see.
Are you sure Olof will
come after you, my Bey?
I'll show myself as Olof's bait.
He will come after me.
However, he will be the bait.
Then I will come too, my Bey.
No.
You will take care of the
Emperor's health.
This is the real trap.
Olof will die.
But you won't take your eyes off them.
Okay, my Bey.
Well.
Come on.
Come, Olof.
The only place you'll follow
me to is your death.
Olof, Osman is starting to move.
Nice.
Don't forget, we will kill Osman when
we see him.
Today, our black curse will be
upon Osman...
and then upon all the Turks, come on.
Commander Olof!
Emperor Andronikos is waiting for you.
We don't want to make our emperor wait.
But I have a thing to do.
He is waiting, Olof.
Frodi.
Kill Osman.
And let him taste the death he deserves.
Don't worry, Olof.
Today, Constantinople will be the
tomb of Osman.
You should not have come
to Constantinople, Osman.
Do everything you can.
Now!
Olof is listening to you, speak
up, Emperor.
When you heard of Ophelia's betrayal...
you took action.
This proves your loyalty.
Like the devotion your ancestors showed
over hundreds of years to our ruling family.
We have always been loyal to you.
However, you always trust the
wrong people, Emperor.
Osman works with all of them.
The slaves saved you that day.
Today, they saved Ophelia, and
Osman as well.
You can't trust anyone who
isn't noble like you.
Are you of a noble?
No.
But you have the courage of
someone of noble lineage.
No emperor, I am more
courageous than many nobles.
You were always talking about
the demonic moves of the Turks...
First, they open the wound...
and then they heal it.
In return, they gain
infinite confidence.
Destroy that trust, Emperor.
Tear it up.
Trust?
I am the emperor of Rome, Olof.
Do you think I trust Osman?
I'm thinking of all possibilities, that's
why you're here.
What do you want from me?
Ophelia must go to Osman.
I will give you a strong unit
under your command.
If you are right about your doubts...
kill Ophelia and Osman.
Your faithful servant, Olof, he'll make the
best use of this power you have given him.
I will test Osman for
the last time tomorrow.
And then, death to your enemies!
Come!
Who gives Olof commands?
I don't know anything.
Who is the closest person to
Olof in this mansion?
Emperor Andronikos.
You will speak more.
You will speak.
Kill me.
I decide when to kill you.
tell me.
Where is Olof?
Where?
Soldiers, kill them all!
It will not end here, Osman.
Turhan.
Osman.
Osman was waiting for us, Olof.
Is there a spy among you?
How does he know?
Thank Odin.
You are important for Frigg.
Otherwise, I would have cut off
your head a long time ago.
Allow me to make it up.
Let me kill Osman.
Even if I would die for it...
I will not die.
I will not die before I kill Osman.
He is mine now.
I will burn him alive on the land
where he was born.
Rivers will be filled with blood.
The soil will be wet with their blood
I swear to Odin...
I will run over everyone who
comes out in front of me.
If they threw arrows at him so he wouldn't
speak, that means we got close, my Bey.
However, they continue with
their games. (tricks)
We will make the game even bigger.
You will persuade Ophelia
to come to Yenişehir.
I'll make her face Kantakuzenos.
If she's innocent, she's in danger.
We will protect her.
If she's not innocent...
I'm the one who will
hold her accountable.
Olof will come to your land.
I've put a unit under his command
and they're getting ready.
Even if it is Olof who leads them, the
soldiers are my soldiers.
I want you to host them well, Osman.
They will find Ophelia.
Who did you take permission from?
I trusted our friendship, Osman Bey.
Moreover, Ophelia is our common enemy.
This land is under my rule.
Ophelia is my enemy.
But Olof is not my friend.
Osman Bey, I will go in and
bring my enemy, even if they're in hell
- Even if they are in your la...
- Shut up
This land you are trying to enter
is filled with corpses of people like you.
Osman Bey.
Olof will stick to your words.
And with my command, he will bring
my daughter to me.
Have you ever obtained my permission
while entering my city?
If we are friends, you have to prove it.
So he'll stick to my words, huh?
That's not enough.
We need more than this.
I am listening to you.
What do you want?
Now that we are talking
about a friendship...
...we need to build a structure.
I will assign the person I see fit
in that building.
If we are talking about friendship...
...this is how you become my friend.
What will you gain from this, Emperor?
The under of Emperor's palace is full of
secret passages.
Those passages are full of demons.
I will protect the emperor.
There is no need for this concession.
I'll clear the way with my axe, Emperor.
An embassy?
This is something that only
happens between great states.
Are you that great?
If we are talking about present time...
I'm great enough for you to
owe me your life.
But if we are talking about the past...
We are great enough to impose taxes
on your state, as Attila did.
As for the future, we will see it together.
We'll see together who's the greatest.
We always say "one for all, all for one"
And if you don't accept this,
that means you're testing my greatness.
Rome is here, Osman Bey.
But where is Attila?
You are talking to him.
You have to agree with me.
I will open an embassy for you, Osman bey.
And you will open your land to Olof.
Kantakuzenos will be busy with the trial
of Oktem Bey.
Peace will last forever.
No one will test the other.
As long as you don't raise your sword,
I'll always shake your hand.
But in the contrary case...
I will kill whoever you send to my land.
Emperor.
I am going back to my hometown.
Kumaral Abdul
will take care of your health.
As long as we're friends...
...I am with you.
Yenisehir
You have nowhere to run to anymore.
We'll talk.
Mother, not now.
You cool off first, otherwise we may upset
each other.
Aktemur!
I say we'll talk.
So we'll talk.
Son...
...I know that you
fell in love with that girl.
- Mother, you...
- Mothers always know, Aktemur!
I know my son.
I also see where this road leads.
There is no end on this road!
I don't constent to that girl, Aktemur!
I don't want to upset you.
But it's heart, mother.
You can't just forget.
You have to!
I will make you forget!
Son.
A lover cannot harm her lover.
When you love someone,
you do everything to protect them.
You do not stab him in the chest!
It was a mistake, mother!
Alcicek is innocent.
I don't care whether or not!
You will stay away from that girl.
I will not take
that girl for you, Aktemur!
She hurt me while trying
to protect me, mother!
I wouldn't have released
her if she was guilty!
So are you the one who decides that?
Subasi!
You did not do your job properly!
For you, that girl comes first
before your job, Aktemur!
What a shame.
Mother.
Your words are heavy.
Aktemur,
I'll never see you around that girl again.
This is my last warning.
Beautiful, really beautiful fabrics.
These came from Constantinople.
It is as fine as the fabrics
of your clothes.
Don't worry.
Never seen such a dumb flirting.
Have you been to Constantinople before?
Is this a part of our game?
What do you say to him, huh?
I said I grew up in Constantinople.
No, where is he?
He is in Constantinople.
I'm sure of this.
Beautiful, I really like the fabrics.
All my clothes should
be sewn with these fabrics.
What a never ending talk!
It's just a damn fabric.
Like they're preparing for a wedding.
Come on.
When I lost that snake Frig
in the alley, Marta was there too.
I never trust that woman.
The trouble came when Marta came.
Ayse, tell our sisters to keep an eye
on her.
I sent them after her in the morning.
According to our sisters,
Sir Liu is not seen in the market.
We also didn't find that wounded dog
that went to prison that day.
I don't understand.
They are both inside us.
We will find them Malhun.
Once Ulgen arrives, we'll find out
about that Marta.
Inshallah.
Can I come in, Malhun Hatun?
Come in Ulgen.
That infidel Hatun is too picky!
It's just a fabric and they can't decide!
They talk over and over.
What did they talk about?
Do you think they know each other?
I don't know.
They spoke a foreign language,
I didn't understand a single word
Try to remember.
Maybe they told a familiar word?
I heard the word Constantinople.
Other than that,
they just giggled and cackled.
That Marta or whatever is her name,
she set her eyes on that man.
There must be something in this.
We had better follow that Marta.
Let's see what she hides.
It'll fit Kantakuzenos perfectly.
I brought the fabrics you asked, Marta.
Osman, that was the reason
for your absence.
You've healed the emperor but
you are coming back alone.
Get ready.
We will greet Osman Bey.
Yes madam.
Bala Hatun.
There's news from my Bey,
he's approaching.
Good then, prepare you alps, Boran.
I'll come too, we'll go together.
Eyvallah (alright)
Don't be afraid princess, it's me.
Sarkis.
My father...
How is he?
Did you see him? Is he alive?
He's alive, ma'am.
He is conscious.
Jesus the High,
you heard my prayer!
Osman Bey.
His healer saved your father.
They found the antidote.
Osman.
Should I trust him?
Or is this part of the game?
I don't know, Sarkis!
My mind is so confused!
I also have the same doubts, princess.
But Osman Bey saved your father
from death for the second time.
If you consider all the help he lended...
He is still a Turk.
He must have an interest.
You are right, princess.
But there are people
who want to kill you in this city.
Also they think I am a vile reptilian
who wants to kill her father!
They want to kill both me
and my reputation, Sarkis.
You can't stay here
until your innocence is proven.
It seems that going to
Yenişehir is in your best interest.
Those who want to kill me
also want to kill my father, Sarkis.
On top of that,
I don't even know who they are.
How can I leave my father?
There are hundreds of soldiers loyal
to the emperor who can protect him.
But I am afraid that even your father can't
protect you from this slander against you.
What are we going to do now?
Osman Bey!
My Bey! Osman Bey!
Attack.
Kill.
Remove them.
Who are you?
I brought you death.
Osman.
Come to me then.
We are coming my Bey!
Do you always set an ambush to win,
ignoble dog!?
Now I will shed your and Osman's blood.
Cerkutay!
I have an eye behind my head!
No one can save you from me now!
Maybe not today but tomorrow.
Bala, alps!
Bala.
You are fine, right?
I'm fine Osman, I'm fine
But I missed that woman who
haunts our children!
No.
We are riding our horses to protect our
children from them.
Come.
First our children, then you.
How many attacks has it been, my Osman?
But thank Allah you are here safe and sound.
As long as I have a wife
like you standing behind me...
...no ambush can hurt us
Let them attack.
But their swords do not hurt our heart.
So tell me, did you see her face?
No my Bey.
She clearly doesn't want to be recognized.
Well, who do you suspect?
There is one I doubt.
Let's get to Yenişehir and we'll know.
Let's go, let's go.
Let's go, Alps!
If you allow me, my Bey,
the training is over.
Brother, take me with you this time.
I don't have anything to do.
I'll help you there.
Your job is to stay here
and take care of your sister.
But she always sleeps,
I have nothing to do.
Brother Aladdin, will you also
go with brother Orhan?
No sister.
I will go to school in Konya
if Osman Bey permits.
You're all leaving me!
Luckily I have a sister.
Aladdin.
Face me.
Come on, raise your sword.
Let's go.
Are you running away
to school now, Aladdin?
Why would you say that, brother?
I am not running away.
I know your problem
is not with me brother.
But if you have something to say,
face our father and tell him.
You can't achieve anything by running away.
I'm not running away, brother.
Everyone think I am such a coward and weak.
So they consider everything
I do is running away.
Excuse me, brother.
I have to go to school now.
Life is hard, brother.
And you will learn, too.
You will grow up and mature anyway.
My brave brother.
We can face the whole world together,
with the heart of yours!
Can I come in, my Bey?
Are you alone, Huseyin?
Yes my Bey!
Come.
Did you figure it out?
What happened to the gold?
Where did all this gold go?
Didn't he make a pact with the emperor?
It is clear that the gold
goes to Constantinople.
There was a lot of gold.
Considering that the heads of this plan
sacrifice so much gold...
...maybe...
...we can find more than this
if we keep tracking.
You didn't understand, did you, Huseyin?
- I didn't understand, my Bey.
- You'll understand, you'll understand.
What I mean is...
...in which scenario do I earn more?
Should I sell Olof to Osman...
Or should I sell Osman to Olof?
Our Oktam Bey will be fine but...
...we should think it through.
Check carefully throughout the tribe.
Who knows, maybe there's
more gold somewhere else.
As you order, my Bey!
Welcome, Osman Bey.
Here you go, Osman Bey.
Host your infidel guest the best!
Make sure your guest feels comfortable.
However, I will not let you
have my Bey.
Let's hope that Osman Bey realizes
his mistake.
Otherwise, there will be a bloodshed.
Their justice is
in favor of the infidels, my daughter.
Come on, don't waste your time.
Take a good look around.
Did that Kantakuzenos dog
get out of the mansion?
- No, he's not out yet. He's still in.
- Good.
Go and check around.
And when that dog comes out,
we'll take him down.
Your father's innocence is up to him.
Sisters, go straight to Marta's shop.
Alcicek.
Alcicek Hatun.
What are you doing here?
Don't you have another job?
Are you watching me?
Well...
It's hard to tell what's your next move is.
I wanted to warn you beforehand.
- Why did you come?
- What do you think?
What are my people going to eat, Subasi?
I am managing our stall in the market.
Alps!
Please escort Alcicek Hatun
to her stall.
Keep your eyes on her.
There is no need for this, Subasi.
Hatun.
Either alps accompany you...
...or you will return to your tent.
Alcicek!
You turned our tribe into a prison.
Now, are you going to make
Yenisehir a prison for us, Subasi?
Come on
Go to the stall.
Subasi.
Keep your eyes off my daughter, Subasi.
Otherwise, I will gouge your eyes out.
What are you talking about, Bengi Hatun?
I am...
If we take in a bit more,
it will fit perfectly.
How long will this woman stay here?
I'll find a way to get her out of here.
I can do this another way too.
Speak our language.
Or do your job without talking.
Where is your wound?
Either the shooter is not skilled
...or he didn't want to kill you.
A fly bite does not kill a lion.
That wound is unimportant.
Where have you been, Osman Bey?
Did you have these clothes stitch?
Yes.
Tailored by our best tailors.
Get this Hatun out of the mansion.
I come from Constantinople.
Why?
They poisoned the emperor.
Don't worry, he's fine.
You showed me the darkness first, then you
showed me the light, Osman Bey.
There is a lot of information
I have to tell you.
But they're not good news.
-What does that mean?
-Can I come in, my Bey?
Come.
My Bey, Dursun has come.
Let's solve Oktem Bey issue first.
Let's go to the court.
Marta.
Prince Kantakuzenos.
I hope he likes his dress.
Yes, yes.
He was very grateful.
It is very important to
make the guest happy.
Marta!
I was looking for you in the sky.
I found you on earth.
I am here
Bala Hatun.
I am coming from the market.
I stopped by the shop, but...
I couldn't see both you and Leo.
So you were here.
Sometimes you just can't see them
even if they're just in front of you.
My brother Leo went to
Constantinople to get fabric.
And I'm here for the prince.
So...
Why were you looking for me?
For fabric.
Marta.
I wanted to see the new fabrics.
What you are wearing is...
...very eye-catching.
You deserve better.
But I have a lot of these fabrics.
When you stop by, I'll show you,
Bala Hatun.
Excuse me now.
Of course.
I will visit you someday.
Anytime you want.
But I'm not available today.
I will hand over the fabrics.
What happened, Bala?
We got very close to that snake Frig,
Malhun Hatun.
Very close.
Are you okay?
What happened to your hand?
I'm fine fine, I'll tell you.
Ayse, inform Aktemur.
- We'll follow her.
- Alright.
Let's see what she is hiding.
Let's go to the healer first...
Hurry up, I'm in a hurry
Let's see if you're
clear or dirty, Marta.
Ayse, take care of it here.
Aktemur, let's go.
Alcicek!
- Here.
- Ayse Hatun?
I have heard about you.
Aktemur pitied you.
And he didn't say anything to you
But I am not like Aktemur.
I have no mercy.
Did he pity me?
Did he?
Let him know.
He should never pity us.
Tell him, I won't pity him either.
You will be punished for your actions.
You will answer to Osman Bey, Alcicek.
I haven't done anything I can't answer.
I am here, responsible for all my acitons.
Now get out of my way.
You can definitely answer.
But you can't pay for what you did
to my son.
I don't want to see
you around my son again.
Go now.
Pity, huh? Subasi!
You will cause trouble for my son.
But I won't allow you.
Here.
Kantakuzenos...
...wants Oktem Bey to pay.
With the court...
...we'll reveal the truth
one way or another.
Since the guilt is so clear,
the court makes no sense.
Oktem Bey is guilty.
The reason for court to take place...
...is to show the truth in public.
The evidence proves Oktem Bey guilty.
However...
There is no judgment to be decided now.
Let the court reveal...
...who is guilty and who is not.
Boran!
Come here.
How can you make him face me?
His hands are not even tied!
Kantakuzenos.
Oktem Bey.
Why do you disobey?
For the same reason why you disobeyed
the Sultan and the Vizier.
I disobey for the right.
And for the sake of justice, Osman Bey.
I was considered a disobedient
because I did not trust their justice.
Why don't you trust my justice?
You oppose Turgut Bey.
You raise your sword to Kantakuzenos.
These are already a crime.
What's more, you are involved in
the gold issue.
That's a slander.
If it is true and not slander, I will cut
your head and hang it in your tribe.
Eyvallah (okay).
Dursun Fakih will judge you.
If this court won't cut Oktem Bey's head,
then there's no need for it, Osman Bey.
Whether the evidence proves
Oktem Bey guilty or not...
Neither you nor I can be sure about that.
Only the court will decide that.
Then I will secure my own justice.
I will come with a great
army from Constantinople...
...and the agreement will be over.
Neither you can end the agreement
nor you can come with a great army.
What do you mean?
Are you testing my power, Osman Bey?
Stay patient.
We'll hear everything.
Everyone, go out.
Except for Kantakuzenos.
We are being followed.
Let me see.
Be careful.
Come on, keep your eyes open.
I will learn whom you are after and
what you are up to. I'll know everything.
Tell me, Osman Bey.
I want to know everything.
The emperor does not trust you.
Felic, Ophelia and you...
He thinks you have ambitions for the throne.
What?
Stupid man.
What caused this thought of his...
...while I covered his back.
Did you cause this thought?
Can it be because of your acts?
Olof was with me in Constantinople.
Did you send him?
Yes, I sent him.
To catch the traitor named Ophelia.
And now he's chasing you.
He will kill you at the first opportunity
he gets, by order of the Emperor.
No.
No, something like this can't happen.
Even if the emperor gave such an order...
Olof is loyal to me.
He won't do such thing.
Well, I warned you.
Take precautions if you want.
Are your soldiers enough?
Olof will kill me, huh?
If you side with me, I will protect you.
Will the Prince of Rome seek help
from a Turk?
Go then.
When you leave the borders of Yenişehir...
...your executioners
will be waiting for you.
What do we do then?
Boran.
My Bey.
Take dear Prince to
the secret place.
He's under our protection.
As you order, my Bey.
Oh Alcicek!
How could you do that to a young boy.
Is he still not able to hear?
Yes my Bey!
He doesn't hear, my Bey.
But he acts like he hears!
When will he hear?
It will take some time, my Bey.
But he will hear again.
He has to track.
You'll take care of it, Kumral Abdal.
I can track my Bey!
Who do you want me to find?
Tracing is done, Cerkutay.
We need your sword now.
Kumral Abdal.
Tell me where Olof is.
He lives near Macri, my Bey.
On the rocky beach.
Their place is secured.
They are crowded.
You are doing your job properly,
Kumral Abdal.
Now the enemy is clear.
You know what to do.
Now listen to me very carefully.
Stop!
I told you to stop!
Marta.
Bala Hatun?
What's going on?
Check her, alps!
Bala Hatun.
Why don't you say something?
Did we make a mistake?
We only carry fabrics.
Don't mind me, Marta.
Inspection is required as a precaution.
Here comes the fabric merchant.
Oh my great God!
You scared me so much, Bala Hatun.
There is nothing to be scared of, Marta.
Bala Hatun!
We need you!
It's Aktemur Bey!
Let's go alps!
How sadly, how upsetting.
They shot Aktemur Bey, Bala Hatun!
Son!
Alps, get in the position!
Aktemur, son!
Open your eyes, son!
Son, are you okay, son?
Aktemur, hold on, son!
Hold on!
This bow...
My Allah! They trapped me!
Bala Hatun!
The shooter of Aktemur is here!
Move!
- What have you done, Alcicek!
- Bala Hatun.
- I was...
- Shut up
Aktemur.
I didn't do this.
- I was ne...
- I told you to shut up!
Let's go to Yenişehir quickly,
he's seriously injured!
Imprison Alcicek.
I did not do this!
My love!
We didn't succeed, we didn't!
We didn't succeed this time either!
Osman is alive.
Your anger, your anger is
what binds me to you.
Don't worry.
I will remove Osman.
I came with an army from Constantinople.
Osman will die.
I've never smelt death like this.
Tell me.
Oktem's trial...
...will carry our black curse to Yenişehir
And Yenişehir will get to meet Frig.
Oh my love.
Painting my face and
hugging you on the battlefield...
I've been waiting for this war
for a long time.
No.
This is not a war.
This will be our slaughter.
mumbling
Come in, hurry up!
Don't scream!
He'll hear!
He has become deaf,
he will not hear us, my daughter.
Hurry up, let's put the blanket on
before he wakes up
He surely has an eye behind his head.
Take it, daughter.
Evil eyes shall stay away!
The ones with evil eye shall crack!
Enviers shall suffer!
Their ears shall break!
Against the evil eyes!
Get out now!
There is an evil eye!
Cerkutay.
Cerkutay wouldn't die!
I was immortal?!
Did I die???
I guess I died in the war.
No.
The war hasn't started yet.
I didn't go to the war.
Oh so this is a dream.
My plate is empty.
There's no food.
I don't have a dream where
I don't eat.
They must have poisoned me.
That woman Ulgen Hatun
must have poisoned me!
Do you mean me, Cerkutay?
A nightmare!
No, no, no, it's a nightmare!
Just go back to sleep.
Go back to sleep now.
Do we know the shooter of Kantakuzenos?
Someone is playing a game here,
but we will know soon.
We will know it all.
Kantakuzenos is under my control.
Olof's place is also known.
There is also Oktem Bey.
I am sure about his innocence,
but we need a proof.
Yes.
They grit their teeth
and we grit our teeth
But when the dog shows his tooth...
We'll bite that dog on the neck.
Now that we know
where that dog Olof is...
...we must kill him after
what he has done to us.
The emperor sent Olof.
We will not kill Olof and go against
the Emperor now.
Even the emperor does business
behind our back.
He thinks we don't realize.
Let them setup the game.
But we will rule them.
My Allah!
Slander is a very deep well.
A very dark well it is.
There is no evidence of my innocence
on the earth.
Your Messenger, with his beautiful face,
had a torn shirt, at least.
But I am facing this slander...
...all helpless, all naked, my Creator.
My Allah, I have no one else
to seek help but You.
You know what's the secret.
And you light up the darkness.
Save me from this well, my Creator.
Amen.
Leave me, leave me!
leave me!
I told you to leave me, leave me!
Alcicek.
leave me!
Father.
What is this about?
What are you doing here, Alcicek?
They played a big game, father.
They wounded Subasi
and blamed me.
That's enough!
This is enough already!
I will not let them get away with this.
I won't, daughter.
Bring a piece of cloth and
hot water quickly!
Come on, hold on, my valiant!
Hold on Aktemur.
Aktemur! Aktemur!
What happened?
What happened Bala?
What happened? Who did this?
Ayse, I'll tell you.
He was hit by two arrows, the wounds
are critical.
Let's take off his clothes,
let's take off his clothes
Son!
Wait, Aktemur!
Aktemur!
Give me the cloth!
Who did this?
The daughter of Oktem Bey.
- Alcicek.
- What?
This is unbelievable!
She wouldn't!
Why would she do that?
That snake!
I knew she would do something.
I told you to stay away from her!
You didn't listen to me, Aktemur!
Hold on!
Hold on, dear, I'm here!
Aktemur!
We must take them out.
We should take them out.
So, Osman Bey...
...one more time,
we are alone wolves again.
The one who is in a difficult situation
has few friends.
Who said we will be crowded
when we reach our goal?
Vuslat (The ultimate union)
is one home.
Home is the whole world.
Eyvallah.
So what stops us is not fear of death.
No.
We will erase them.
Can I come in, my Bey?
Come!
My Bey!
It's Aktemur.
He is seriously injured.
What?
Protect him, my Allah.
Let him see his mother again.
I didn't do it.
I wouldn't.
No, Bengi sister, no.
They chose Oktem Bey
as a sacrifice.
Otherwise, all these misfortunes
cannot happen at the same time.
I'm sure of that!
Our reputation reaches the
seven seas, Bayindir Bey.
The ones who want to sacrifice us
will be punished dearly.
We'll go through this.
These days will surely pass.
Of course we will.
Every cloud has a silver lining.
Can I come in, Bengi Hatun?
Come!
Alcicek Hatun tried to kill
Gunduz Bey's son Aktemur.
What are you saying?
Alcicek!
I told her not to...
I told her not to act crazy!
Is Aktemur Bey alive?
What is the situation?
I do not know.
They took her to prison.
I will burn Yenisehir!
It is enough!
What they have taken from me is enough!
Alps!
We'll crush everyone.
Get ready.
O Healer!
Who did this?
Tell me!
Hatuns, tell me who did this!
Son.
He is entrusted to me by my brother.
My Bey, it's Oktem Bey's daughter.
Alcicek did this.
That girl, that girl!
She did it in a treacherous way!
She set the trap!
How could she do this to my son?!
Alcicek.
Aktemur.
Open your eyes!
Aktemur!
Calm down, Ayse.
Open your eyes!
Aktemur!
We will erase the devil.
They know how judicious we are,
and they use this.
I swear we'll hang them on the gallows!
Aktemur!
My Allah!
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com